<package>
	<id>com.yexc.messagesxi</id>
	<name>MessagesXI</name>
	<version>1.1-1</version>
	<compatibility>
		<firmware>
			<miniOS>11.0</miniOS>
		</firmware>
	</compatibility>
	<dependencies>
		<package>mobilesubstrate</package>
        <package>ws.hbang.common</package>
	</dependencies>
	<shortDescription>Enhance your Messages app!</shortDescription>
	<descriptionlist>
		<description>
            <![CDATA[
            <strong>What is MessagesXI?</strong>
            <br/><br/>
            I wrote this to initially fix an annoyance of mine within the Messages app and is my first publicly published tweak! Since then, it has some features I would like to outline:
            <br/>

            <ul>
                <li>If you background or close out Messages when selected on a message, you will be pushed back to your list of messages instead of staying on the previously selected one (what I originally wrote this for).
                </li>
                <li>The ability to read/unread messages manually! If this option is enabled, you will see a "Read" or "Unread" depending on if you actually have unread messages. You can also swipe to the right to read/unread on the chat
                </li>
                <li>Hide the typing indicator (3 dots) from the other person</li>
                <li>Delete all conversations in list while editing</li>
            </ul>
            ]]>
        </description>
        
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
            <strong>Limitations</strong>
            <br/>
            
            <ul>
                <li>Because of how Apple has implemented the backend of each message, unreading the chat will not takeaway a read receipt for the other party, if that is enabled. What MessagesXI will do is put the blue dot beside the message you decided to unread. This is the best way to mark a message and come back to it if needed. This also means you will not see a badge on Messages but can be implemented if there is enough support
                </li>
            </ul>
            ]]>
        </description>

        <description>
            <![CDATA[
            <strong>Cool things</strong>
            <br/>
            
            <ul>
                <li>It would be annoying if you have to manually hit read once you send a message. I decided to read the message once a message is sent but never before that. This same concept also applies to group messages!
                </li>
            </ul>
            ]]>
        </description>
        
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
            <strong>Compatibility</strong>
            <br/>
            
            <ul>
                <li>I only tested this on my iPhone X, iOS 13.2.3 and iPhone 7+, iOS 13.3</li>
                <li>arm64 and arm64e support (A12/A13 devices)</li>
                <li>iOS 11/12/13 support</li>
                <li><strong>If anything does not work for you, please email me!</strong></li>
            </ul>
            ]]>
        </description>
        
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
            <strong>Future plans</strong>
            <br>
            <small>Not all plans will be listed</small>
            <br/>
            
            <ul>
                <li>+1 to Messages badge if unreading message</li>
            </ul>
            ]]>
        </description>
	</descriptionlist>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot>
			<description>The option to unread a message when there ARE NO actual unread messages is displayed in the top right of the navigation bar</description>
			<image>read.PNG</image>
		</screenshot>		
		<screenshot>
			<description>The option to read a message when there ARE unread messages is displayed in the top right of the navigation bar</description>
			<image>unread.PNG</image>
		</screenshot>		
	</screenshots>
	<changelog>
        <change>Bug fix for swiping/long press to read</change>
        <change>Support for iOS 11/12, Add ability to hide typing indicator, Add ability to delete all conversations, Add ability to swipe to read/unread</change>
        <change>Add ability to choose not to automatically read group chats</change>
		<change>Initial release</change>
	</changelog>
	<links>
		<link>
			<name>Release post</name>
            <url>https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak/comments/fg5jql/release_messagesxi_enhance_your_messages_app</url>
			<iconclass>fa fa-reddit</iconclass>
		</link>
	</links>
</package>
